https://digikam.org/support/privacy_policy/

Privacy PolicyThe digiKam Team built the Google Photo, Google Drive or another
Webservices uploader as a open source app. This SERVICE is provided by
the digiKam Team at no cost and is intended for use as is.This page is used to inform website visitors regarding our policies with
the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone
decided to use our Service.If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and
use of information in relation with this policy. The Personal
Information that we collect are used for providing and improving the
Service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as
described in this Privacy Policy.The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our
Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at Webservices uploader,
unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.Information Collection and UseFor a better experience while using our Service, we may require you to
provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including
but not limited to pictures. The information that we request is will be
retained by us and used as described in this privacy policy.The app does use third party services that may collect information used
to identify you.Log DataWe want to inform you that whenever you use our Service, in case of an
error in the app we collect data and information (through third party
products) on your computer called Log Data. This Log Data may include
information such as your devices’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address,
device name, operating system version, configuration of the app when
utilising our Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and
other statistics.CookiesCookies are files with small amount of data that is commonly used an
anonymous unique identifier. These are sent to your browser from the
website that you visit and are stored on your devices’s internal memory.This Services does not uses these “cookies” explicitly. However, the app
may use third party code and libraries that use “cookies” to collection
information and to improve their services. You have the option to either
accept or refuse these cookies, and know when a cookie is being sent to
your device. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to
use some portions of this Service.Service ProvidersWe may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following
reasons:To facilitate our Service;To provide the Service on our behalf;To perform Service-related services; orTo assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.We want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have
access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks
assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to
disclose or use the information for any other purpose.SecurityWe value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we
are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But
remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of
electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee
its absolute security.Links to Other SitesThis Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a
third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these
external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you
to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over,
and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or
practices of any third-party sites or services.Children’s PrivacyThis Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not
knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under
13. In the case we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with
personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If
you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has
provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will
be able to do necessary actions.Changes to This Privacy PolicyWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are
advised to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify
you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These
changes are effective immediately, after they are posted on this page.Contact UsIf you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do
not hesitate to contact us.This Privacy Policy page was created at
privacypolicytemplate.net.digiKam Recipes BookLatest NewsdigiKam 7.2.0-beta1 is releaseddigiKam 7.1.0 is releaseddigiKam Recipes 20.07.27 releaseddigiKam 7.0.0 is releaseddigiKam 7.0.0-rc is releaseddigiKam news
